Francis Efobi

Web Developer

Web Developer with 1 year of experience specializing in freelancing and designing websites for Startups. I am aiming to expand my professional horizon within my field. My greatest strength is my ability to work as a team player to help achieve organizational goals.

Experience

2020-11 - Freelance Graphics & UI/UX Designerpresent Designing Logos and High-Fidelity Mockupfor Startups

2021-02 - IT Staff

2021-07 Paxson Nigeria Company Limited

- Responsible for tracking of Warehouse operations and accounting operations.
- Assistant computer technician.

2020-01 - Web developer & Network Technician2021-01 Obidon ICT Hub

- Designing and tutoring students on Web development.
- Hardware and CISCO networking equipment maintenance.

Education & Certificates

2018 - Andela Learning Community
2019 Android Development Beginner & Advance Bundle.

2016-09 - National Diploma2018-07 Federal Polytechnic Nekede, Owerri, Imo State.

Computer Science

2008-09 - West African Senior School Certificate

2011-08 Winners International School, Nkpor, Anambra

State.

Personal Info

Address

85 Limca Road Nkpor, Anambra State.

Nationality

Nigerian

Phone

+234 810-984-3018

E-mail

francisefobi@gmail.com

Github

github.com/Efobi-Francis

Skills

Core Java, HTML5, CSS

Corel Draw, Adobe XD

CISCO network technician, Computer OS maintenance

MS office

Communication Skills

Strategic Planning